{"data":[{"question":"Your clothes ___ dirty; you must have ___ washed.","a":"are, it","b":"is, it","c":"are, them","d":"is, them","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Clothes (plural)-are, them","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"That is a ___ report.","a":"ten-thousand-word","b":"ten-thousand-words","c":"ten-thousands-word","d":"ten-thousands-words","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n-Compound Adjectives with Numbers: number+ name of thing : always  in singular\n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"There are eight _________  in our school.","a":"Smiths'","b":"Smith's","c":"Smiths's","d":"Smiths","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- When a family name (a proper noun) is pluralized, we almost always simply add an \"s.\"\n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Miss Stevenson is a friend of ___.","a":"Kelly's mother","b":"Kelly's mother's","c":"Kelly mother's","d":"Mother's of Kelly","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Kelly's mother's = Kelly's mother's friends: means that her mother has many friends and Miss Stevenson is one of them","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"We sent Helen ___ when she passed her examination.","a":"the congratulation","b":"our congratulations","c":"our congratulation","d":"a congratulation","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Congratulations (plural): words saying you are happy that someone has achieved something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"You are as clever as ___.","a":"your sister is","b":"your sister's","c":"our congratulation","d":"of your sister","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the comparison of equality","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Please give ___ to your parents.","a":"a regard","b":"the regard","c":"my regard","d":"my regards","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Regards [plural]: good wishes - used when sending your good wishes to someone or when ending a short letter or message","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Playing badminton is ___ in any season.","a":"very fun","b":"a great fun","c":"great fun","d":"great funs","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Fun: uncoutable noun which is always treated as singular\n\n- Don't use article (a,an,the) when mentions things in general","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Where did you get these ___?","a":"watchs","b":"watch","c":"watch's","d":"watches","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Noun end with \"sh, ch...\" = plural: noun + es","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Nancy went to the ___ last Friday to buy a pair of shoes.","a":"shoes store","b":"shoe's store","c":"shoes' store","d":"shoe store","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"}]}